Do you think the coast is clear?
人们是否已远离?
No one to see, no one to hear
没人注视, 没人在意
Me sing out my song?
我独自颂唱?
I think we're all alone
我们无人陪同
I don't need my name in lights
不用名声随光而来
That's not where I set my sights
那不是我要的精彩
No, oh-oh, no, not me
不, 噢 噢 不 歌曲
I don't need a stage to sing
不用舞台也尽兴
I like the quiet, I like the calm
我酷爱平静, 不爱张扬
To turn it up, to sing along
调高音量, 独自歌唱
I'm not just shy
不止害羞
Look close, and you will see
靠近你能明析
There's so much more to me
另一面在心底
I'm just fine rehearsing on my own
独自唱~歌自在又心动
My hairbrush is my microphone
毛刷是我的麦克风
Look out now, I'm in the zone
请看好, 灵感迸冲
Yeah!
耶!
Can you feel it?
能否感受?
I like the quiet, I like the calm
我酷爱平静, 不爱张扬
To turn it up, to sing along
调高音量, 独自歌唱
I'm not just shy
不止害羞
Look close, and you will see
靠进, 你能明析
There's so much more to me
另一面在心底
I speak soft out in a crowd
我说话声音很小
I whisper, "am I being too loud?"
总自问, "我是不是太吵?"
But when I close that door
一但有地方躲
The crowd, it just wants more and more and more
将听到我唱更多更多更多~
I like the quiet, I like the calm
我酷爱平静, 不爱张扬
To turn it up, to sing along
调高音量, 独自歌唱
I'm not just shy
不止害羞
Look close, and you will see
靠近你能明析
There's so much more to me
另一面在心底
I like my friends, I like my pets
我爱朋友, 也爱宠物
I like to rock, do pirouettes
我爱摇滚, 也爱跳舞
I'm more than shy
不止害羞
I'm more than you can see
我有许多秘密
There's so much more to me
总能给你精喜